http://ens-newswire.com/privacy-policy/

Subscribe
Environment News Service Terms and Conditions and Statement of Privacy
Environment News Service is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to Environment News Service Web site and governs data collection and usage at all Environment News Service sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the Environment News Service Statement of Privacy. Environment News Service is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Collection of your Personal Information
Environment News Service accepts email and RSS subscriptions to our free news service.  To send you the news, we collect your email address on a subscription form that you fill out. You may also choose to supply your name, the name of your organization and the country in which you reside, although these data points are not required for you to receive ENS news by email or RSS feed.
Environment News Service encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Environment News Service so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Environment News Service Web site.
Use of your Personal Information
Environment News Service does not sell, rent or lease its subscriber lists to third parties.
Environment News Service may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Environment News Service or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Environment News Service including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Environment News Service or the public.
Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Environment News Service or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Environment News Service abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control your Personal Information
You may stop the delivery of future news or promotional e-mail from Environment News Service by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.
Security of your Personal Information
Environment News Service is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we use a secure payment gateway so your information is protected.
Changes to this Statement
Environment News Service will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Environment News Service will use your personal information, Environment News Service will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Environment News Service encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Environment News Service is protecting your information.
Conditions of Use
Use of the Environment News Service website constitutes agreement to our terms of use. We encourage you to review the following information carefully.
TRADEMARKS
Environment News Service and other marks indicated on our site are trademarks owned exclusively by Environment News Service. The use of these trademarks and trade dress is prohibited if used in connection with the sale of any product that is not Environment News Service’s, in any manner that seeks to disparages or discredit Environment News Service or in any manner that may cause confusion among our customers.
COPYRIGHT
All content on this website is the exclusive property of Environment News Service. Said content includes text, graphics, logos, icons, images, audio and video clips, digital downloads, and software. Our content is protected by United States and international copyright laws and we reserve all rights contained therein. In case of dispute or infringement, we will rigorously defend our rights to this material.
PROTECTING YOUR ACCOUNT
Some portions of this website permit username and passwords to be used. You are responsible for protecting your unique username and password and you agree to be responsible for all activities performed under your user account.
LICENSE AND SITE ACCESS
Environment News Service grants you (the user) a limited license to access and make personal use of this website. This license does not include the right to download any material (other than routine page caching), modify any material, or any portion thereof, without the express written consent of Environment News Service. This license excludes the download or collection of logos, product descriptions, pricing, text, graphics, audio and video clips, and/or copying account information. This website or any portion of this website may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written permission of Environment News Service. You are prohibited from using meta tags or any other hidden text utilizing Environment News Service’s name or trademarks without the express written consent of Environment News Service. Any unauthorized use of this websites voids the limited license granted by Environment News Service.
CONTENT SUBMITTED BY SITE USERS
If you do post content to this site or otherwise submit material (including, but not limited to, photographs and testimonials), you grant Environment News Service and its affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. By your submission you represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify Environment News Service or its affiliates for all claims resulting from content you supply. Environment News Service reserves the right to remove any content at our sole discretion.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
This site is provided by Environment News Service on an “as is” and “as available” basis. Environment News Service makes no warranties, either expressed or implied, as to the operation of the site or the content contained therein. You expressly agree that your use of www.ens-newswire.com is at your own risk.
Environment News Service cannot warrant that this site, our servers, or email communications affiliated with the use of this website, are free from viruses. Environment News Service will not be responsible for any damages of any kind resulting from use of this website, including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, and consequential damages.
APPLICABLE LAW
By visiting www.ens-newswire.com, you agree that the laws of the state of Oregon, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Conditions of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Environment News Service.
CHANGES IN POLICY
Environment News Service reserves the right to modify, alter, delete and update these policies at any time we see fit. Such alterations do not nullify our rights if infringements or breaches occurred under a previous version of these conditions.
REFUND POLICY
Environment News Service does not offer refunds. We have a No Refunds Policy.
Sunny Lewis
Editor in Chief,
Environment News Service
Tel: 541-992-5901
Cel: 206-470-9408
www.ens-newswire.com
Search for:
